All right, castle's down!
They were ready!
I told you!
Sure kept me waiting, little fleas!
We're done for!
I don't know what to do.
Jim
Get moving.
Why does it always fall on me?
Damn it all the hell
Not so fast.
Heavenly.
Die!
Riju!
Ignore her, both of you.
It's her fault for being weak.
Focus on the mission.
He's such a sweetheart.
Don't worry, I'm not done yet.
I might as well start with you!
So long, Jermagirl!
Kum Kum!
Cap-lis-shom-beh! Cross!
I'll make Kum Kum!
It's too bright!
I thought we weren't
supposed to go outside!
No, you're not supposed to go.
I can do whatever I want.
You cheater!
Loopy, no!
Please come back!
There's a monster deep within your dream.
Taking aim for your
heart so it would seem.
To stand tall and read, go to
hell and jump for paradise.
Every time dangerous, dangerous.
We like it serious, serious, oh.
Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain.
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today.
Adventure calls now, let's go.
The balls filled between
us, they will show.
Still what we don't know.
Yes, working hard together.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream to fight the rivalry.
Gotta see it through believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
All the love and the tears
in the world we're in.
United gently bringing up
our thought again, yeah.
We're the foolish ones we love.
We'll carry on till we see the light.
The sun will rise.
The greatest fight at its core.
Is against myself forevermore.
Come on, let's do it now, let's go.
The bonds go between us, they will show.
So what we don't know.
That's what we call adventure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream.
Just like the rivalry.
Gotta see it through.
But living in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Superpowers.
Yes, we're the superpowers.
Superpowers, Superpowers, Superpowers.
Yes, we're the Superpowers, Superpowers.
Yes, we're the Superpowers.
My, my, my, my!
Why are you running away?
Is it because you're
too scared to fight me?
Don't you remember what
you told me, Straw Hat?
The first time we spoke when
you were on Fishman Island,
I believe you said you
were going to kick my ass.
Well then, Monkey D.
Luffy, now that I know
who you are, come here.
Let's chat in the new world.
I like this island.
It's too risky to trust you with it.
Once I get there, I'm gonna kick your ass.
And then I'll make Fishman
Island my territory.
And do you remember what you said to me
when you were captured in my library?
Something about making
me sorry, if I recall.
You haven't become King of the
Pirates, and that's on you.
Nothing else to it.
Get over here and fight me!
I'm not backing down Even
if you are an emperor!
I'm taking Sanji back no matter what!
I'm gonna turn this all
around and make you sorry!
And now you want to run?
I guess you're all talk!
I'm all talk?
She's just trying to provoke you!
Just one punch!
Hey, come back!
I said that stuff and I meant it all!
Now I'll prove it!
Whoop!
You will never be king
of the pirates, Big Mom!
But I will be!
Oh, excellent work!
It sure is nice having
human shields! It's over!
No betrayal shall go unpunished!
I'll burn you to death with my own hands!
This one is scary!
Wondered when an oven was shown?
I'll make sure you suffer! Ah!
You two play nice, okay?
You're not burning anybody, pal.
If you're looking to get pounded in the
face, you're in the right place, though.
That's some faceless confidence.
We're almost there, kid, just keep it up.
What do you think I'm trying to do?
Just so many of them are there.
Yes!
Maybe I won't die after all!
Lickety, let's end this
sticky situation quick!
Candy wall!
Damn it!
What the hell is that
and why is it in my way?
Must be Pierre Sparrow's way!
I'm back to being doomed, aren't I?
My help just fades away.
Aw, nuts!
It's gonna swallow us up!
Turn back! No! Keep going!
We've got this!
Black Bug!
Let's go!
You're clear. What? Really?
A candy wall?
You saved me!
I'm sorry I ever doubted you!
These German guys were
really something else.
They wrecked that candy!
Yo le no!
So scum-do!
I'm so close!
Now that I've made it this far,
I really don't want to die!
Freedom within my sight!
Maybe it's... the candy!
But I swear!
It tastes so sweet!
The Tomatee box is right there!
The secrets could be mine!
I wish it would have fallen
someplace more convenient.
I can't miss this.
I gotta jump.
What are you going to do
with that treasure, Dufeld?
Huh? Who is that?
Stussy, you spying on me?
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
That's smart.
But it'll all be worth it.
The treasure of the deep.
Whatever it is, it's got
to be something good.
Flying Finger Pistol.
The world government will
be claiming the Tomatei Box.
Thank you.
But don't worry.
I'll still let you take the
blame for its disappearance.
I trust that's the story you'll be
writing in your papers, Morgans. Busted!
As long as I can spy what's inside first.
Look, but don't touch.
I'm sure a professional spin doctor such
as yourself knows how
the arrangement works.
I'm a newsman!
That's slander!
What?
Are you kidding me? Ah!
I've got to beat Kaido first.
You're next.
Hey! Crap!
You said just one punch and you got it!
Kaido, you said.
My, my, my, my.
If that little punch
is the best you've got,
he'll make quick work of you, I'm afraid.
But what makes you think
you'll make it that far, huh?
You little bastards are
getting way ahead of yourselves
and you think I'm gonna let
you escape my territory!
Big Mom!
I know that my dream is
dead now, thanks to you!
Long ago, our empire reigned
for a mere sixty-six days,
but the ghosts who cannot return
to their homeland want us still!
How can I face them in defeat?
To think that I trusted
you with their memories,
their cries for
revenge—that have echoed for
three centuries—I can
hardly live with myself.
with myself
Sorry, not enough.
But I'll help you rest in peace, Judge.
I'm going to be making
the whole world peaceful.
Thanks to all the scientific
research I'll be taking from you!
Run, Bethel!
Father!
Did she kill him?
Dad, no!
You've abandoned me!
You're supposed to be
my escort, aren't you?
Why did it have to be Katakuri?
Why did it have to be anybody?
Can't you just let me go?
What a pity.
And you were so close, too.
Don't worry, I haven't abandoned my duty.
You better get moving.
You don't have to ask me twice!
Do you think you'll get
the upper hand that easily?
Or is it that you don't value your life?
If you're trying to
intimidate me, don't bother.
Unfortunately for you,
I don't experience fear.
Keep firing!
Don't let them escape! Yeah!
You can make it!
We're counting on you!
You got this, Caesar!
You scumbag! Hold on!
What was that last part?
Don't get in my way!
Ah?
Move it, you moron!
Who the hell are you, anyway?
You're me?
Wait, that doesn't make sense.
It's me, you fool.
Take a good look.
Ah, Barrel!
Isn't this nice?
Why, I had so much resentment
piling up, I hardly knew what to do.
Now I get to take it all out on you
and your insufferable associates.
Just got ugly.
Look, Caesar.
Our whole team has lost?
It's not fair!
This might be it.
So what do we do?
German, no!
our escape plan has failed they won't rest
to her all dead are you
giving up not at all
but the road ahead is a harsh one
anything beats waiting
for death thankfully i've
still got a bit of fight
left in me i'm going to Yeah,
me too!
And we'll help get your back, too.
If this is the only way.
We were so close, too!
Well, the party's over.
But the executions are next.
What's going on?
A while ago, deep beneath the sea...
Luffy and the Straw Hats had just
saved the Ryugu Kingdom from the new
Fishman Pirates and received the
Tomate Box from King Neptune as thanks.
However...
Please, Your Majesty!
I'm not sure if Luffy
and the others found the
Tomate Box among the stolen
treasures we gave to them,
but, uh, it might be wise to ask them
to give that particular present back!
What are you saying?
I could never ask them to return a
gift that we gave them for saving us.
The problem is it's not exactly treasure.
It's more like a bomb, actually.
What?
It'll explode if they open it?
I must ask them to return it immediately.
You gave the treasure away?
And the big mom no less?
Well, maybe the explosives
are no longer functional.
Very good, Your Majesty.
Misty, I do admire your positivity.
And now, back to the present.
This is the Red Bean Bomb meeting room.
We've got a massive crack running
from the Eastern Bomb second floor.
Not just a crack, it's
split straight in half.
Red Bean Bomb third floor here.
What is going on?
You don't think this is
an earthquake, do you?
We're gonna topple over!
Damn it!
I swear I heard an explosion before this!
So it's an enemy attack!
Doesn't matter!
Let's get going!
Whoever did this will help!
Who wasn't the enemy?
Maybe, but I don't know how.
Who could invade an emperor's home base?
They must have snuck in with a bomb.
Ridiculous, and how the hell
did they get away with it?
Please don't follow us.
I'm going to die, aren't we?
Does this have something to do
with the wedding on the rooftop?
This is a total nightmare,
but it's also big news.
Was there a bomb in
that box, probably yes?
The timing was dead on.
I don't know what else could
have caused it, but why?
Surely they couldn't have planned this.
We're going down.
Hold on tight.
I lost track of the enemy.
Did one of your allies do this?
Beats me, all I know is
that if this didn't happen,
then all of us would be dead for sure.
What was that noise?
What happened to my Shit?
Something or other saved us.
I wouldn't say we're saved just yet.
Far from it, in fact!
We're in big trouble, Mama!
We don't know where,
but an explosion went off and
now the whole Shit is collapsing.
We're going down!
Something's going on out there.
It's kind of weird how we can't
feel anything inside, Beach, huh?
Any idea what might have caused this?
I don't know.
But it's clear.
The situation has devolved into chaos.
Judging from what I can see,
it seems that the Shit itself
is toppling on its side.
What kind of joke is this?
What do you mean, joke?
It's a nightmare.
Damn, see that?
This is a good thing, right?
Who did this?
How is this even possible?
My brothers.
My sisters.
Are they gonna be okay?
I guess so!
Mama!
No!
This is rich.
I don't know who to thank for this, but
they knocked it out of the ballpark.
i don't even gotta knock
off big mom anymore what's
the point look at them the
big mom pirates are Toast!
They're done for!
As good as dead!
The castle is bigger than the whole city!
It doesn't matter if you run or not!
None of us are making it out alive!
Big brother!
Let's stay calm.
This is big news! Really big!
Yeah!
At this rate, you'll take it to the grave.
All right!
I can't fly!
Unreal.
If we really are witnessing the end of
the Big Mom Pirates, Morgan's is right.
That's quite a scoop.
Hey!
Come up here, hurry!
This way!
I think you'd better hurry!
He's got boofy, too!
I figured you were both both.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You two are crazy.
I hope that was worth it.
We're glad that you're back.
Okay, Caesar, let's amskrain.
What, did you think I was going back?
So long, suckers!
I think they're good.
Mission complete.
Let's withdraw.
We're on our way.
Hey, are you all right, pal?
It's too late!
We're done for!
Formatamorphosis!
Giant!
SCREAMING.
That
was
a close one.
Some kind of cream.
What the hell!
It's sponge cave.
What the hell was that?
The whole cake Shit.
It turned into an actual cake.
Nice move.
All this was the head
chef's work, I would guess.
Save the entire family in one fell swoop.
Mama, are you okay?
A cake.
My castle turned into a cake.
Ah, I forgot.
The sweets that Struzan makes with
his ability may fill your stomach,
but don't taste very good. You made it!
I was worried.
What a mess.
Little rats.
Those bastards ruined my wedding cake.
My cake.
Easy does it.
Can I get a hand here? Come on.
Everything will be fine.
I thought I was gone for sure.
I mean, crush my cake!
I heard someone yelling from over there!
Hurry and help them!
Come on.
Look who's here!
Mondore, sir! What happened?
Why did the whole cake
Shit collapse like that?
The entire city got wrecked!
And what's with all this heavy cream?
Shut your traps!
This is not over yet!
Our enemies who plotted to
assassinate mama have gotten away.
We lost their trail, but they
couldn't have gone very far
Hurry and call the tarts
on all total land islands.
We're looking for the Straw Hat pirates
and the fire tank pirates as well.
Don't let a single one of them escape!
I.
Think this is far enough—get out!
out
Thanks for everything, Veggie.
We might be dead if it wasn't for you.
Don't get sappy on me like
I'd ever do a good deed.
Disgusting.
If you're gonna thank
someone, then thank me!
I care with you!
Can it, you loser!
You know, I haven't forgotten what
you did to those kids on Punk Hazard.
We do not need your help anymore.
So go drop dead. Huh? Ah!
Foolish girl!
You should show respect
when you speak to a genius!
Do you want me to turn this entire
island into a wasteland of poison gas?
Because I will!
Huh?
Here.
Take your heart.
I can't believe it.
I never thought this moment would arrive.
You earned your freedom, you scumbag.
You should have crushed it.
No!
Oh, please, please.
Should have crushed it.
My heart!
I'm finally, finally whole again!
So long, suckers!
I'll see you in hell!
Morons!
Simpletons! Nedwins! Good riddance!
Why'd the castle fall?
Seems kind of sudden, huh?
So, do you Karoo know who caused this?
Not the slightest clue!
Pay attention to me, dammit!
Bad news, Father!
Believe it or not, but
the enemy is still alive!
They're a little shaken
up, Lili, but that's all!
The whole Shit turned into a cake, Lili.
Aha.
That would be Strewson's
anti-work, I assume.
That man was a mystery to me.
Who knows what he had cooking.
That is to say, he's
more than just a chef.
He's probably a real tough cookie, too.
I thought the big mom pirates were
kaput after seeing the Shit collapse.
They're lucky to have that guy.
But that's fine.
They still got screwed.
But that makes me feel better.
Would somebody please validate me?
So now we just gotta run away?
Kid, we've been trying to run.
It's just that people
keep getting in our way.
They're gone now.
But let's hurry.
Do as you like, but we're
parting ways. Adios.
Oh, really?
We failed to assassinate Big Mom.
We have no reason to
continue with this alliance.
This guy gets it, but just as a tip:
I'd start hauling ass if I were you,
even after you set sail—it'll take a whole
day to get out of Big Mom's territory.
True enough.
Good luck, you bunch
of wackos, castle tank!
tank
The Straw Hats went that way?
Come on, how petty can that bastard get?
Shove it, pal.
I gotta survive. No fair!
I wanted to give them a
proper farewell le long.
Nami's my friend and we
took off without a word.
Complain later.
Being clear, things might get rough.
Well, guess we'll be on our way.
After retrieving the shark submerged,
we'll take it straight to the
sun and meet up with you there.
Okay, be careful.
We gotta make it all the way to
the coast, so we better hurry.
Daifugo, form two attack units.
You got it.
Soldiers, split up.
We're chasing down the enemy.
Half of you go after Straw Hat,
and the other half will bring
back the head of that traitor,
Buggy.
Mama, listen!
They won't escape.
Don't worry, they'll pay for this.
My cake.
It had the best ingredients,
carefully selected.
It was going to be the queen of all cakes.
This was supposed to be the perfect day.
Give me my wedding cake right now.
Oh no!
Where is my cake?
Why are you hiding my
wedding cake from me?
Please, not now, Mama.
Bring me my wedding cake.
Give it to me now!